{
    "subject":"English Language",
    "topics":
    [
        {
            "topic":"Oral English",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"/ &#8743 / can be seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"cup",
                    "opt2":"pour",
                    "opt3":"poor",
                    "opt4":"dove",
                    "ans":"cup"
                },
                {
                    "question":"/ts/ is seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"chair",
                    "opt2":"shame",
                    "opt3":"shave",
                    "opt4":"chastise",
                    "ans":"chair"
                },

                {
                    "question":"/ &#8706 / can be seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"shove",
                    "opt2":"clear",
                    "opt3":"run",
                    "opt4":"chain",
                    "ans":"shove"
                },
                {
                    "question":"/k/ is seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"comb",
                    "opt2":"simmer",
                    "opt3":"lotion",
                    "opt4":"bring",
                    "ans":"comb"
                },
                {
                    "question":"/U:/ can be seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"pull ",
                    "opt2":"run",
                    "opt3":"dug",
                    "opt4":"do",
                    "ans":"pull"
                },
                {
                    "question":"/b/ can be seen in which word",
                    "opt1":"dumb",
                    "opt2":"bomb",
                    "opt3":"grenade",
                    "opt4":"road",
                    "ans":"bomb"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Antonyms",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"antonyms could also mean",
                    "opt1":"opposites",
                    "opt2":"composition",
                    "opt3":"careful",
                    "opt4":"replaceable",
                    "ans":"opposites"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats an antonym of draw",
                    "opt1":"pull",
                    "opt2":"push",
                    "opt3":"drive",
                    "opt4":"run",
                    "ans":"push"
                },

                {
                    "question":"whats an antonym of remember",
                    "opt1":"know",
                    "opt2":"forget",
                    "opt3":"left",
                    "opt4":"imagine",
                    "ans":"forget"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats an antonym of next",
                    "opt1":"previous",
                    "opt2":"never",
                    "opt3":"courage",
                    "opt4":"none of the above",
                    "ans":"previous"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats an antonym of courage",
                    "opt1":"bravery",
                    "opt2":"cowardice",
                    "opt3":"devil",
                    "opt4":"i don't know",
                    "ans":"cowardice"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats an antonym for the word antonym",
                    "opt1":"similarity",
                    "opt2":"plural",
                    "opt3":"singular",
                    "opt4":"divine",
                    "ans":"similarity"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Synonyms",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"synonyms means",
                    "opt1":"similarities",
                    "opt2":"pluralities",
                    "opt3":"difference",
                    "opt4":"opposite",
                    "ans":"similarities"
                },
                {
                    "question":"the synonym for courage is",
                    "opt1":"bravery",
                    "opt2":"cowardice",
                    "opt3":"euphoric",
                    "opt4":"estatic",
                    "ans":"bravery"
                },

                {
                    "question":"whats is a synonym of qualities",
                    "opt1":"attributes",
                    "opt2":"quantities",
                    "opt3":"neither",
                    "opt4":"all",
                    "ans":"attributes"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats is a synonym of center",
                    "opt1":"middle",
                    "opt2":"between",
                    "opt3":"both",
                    "opt4":"none",
                    "ans":"both"
                },
                {
                    "question":"whats is a synonym of devil",
                    "opt1":"satan",
                    "opt2":"serpent",
                    "opt3":"underground",
                    "opt4":"hate",
                    "ans":"satan"
                },
                {
                    "question":"synonyms are very essential in english language",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Figures of Speech",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"a metaphor makes use of 'as' or 'like'",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },
                {
                    "question":"The boy acts like a cat is what figure of speech",
                    "opt1":"simile",
                    "opt2":"metaphor",
                    "opt3":"oxymoron",
                    "opt4":"euphemism",
                    "ans":"simile"
                },

                {
                    "question":"oxymoron juxtaposes two similar but contrasting words",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },
                {
                    "question":"What is the giving of attributes owned by living things to that of non-living things",
                    "opt1":"personification",
                    "opt2":"euphemism",
                    "opt3":"simile",
                    "opt4":"catharsis",
                    "ans":"personification"
                },
                {
                    "question":"each of the following is a figure of speech except",
                    "opt1":"simile",
                    "opt2":"metaphor",
                    "opt3":"personification",
                    "opt4":"interjection",
                    "ans":"interjection"
                },
                {
                    "question":"'The statue moves freely' is what figure of speech",
                    "opt1":"simile",
                    "opt2":"personification",
                    "opt3":"metaphor",
                    "opt4":"oxymoron",
                    "ans":"personification"
                }
                
            ]
        }
        
    ]
}
